<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing-Automation on N Design Studio</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/categories/marketing-automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing-Automation on N Design Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/categories/marketing-automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WhatConverts: The Complete Guide to Lead Tracking &amp;amp; Marketing Attribution Software (Features, How It Works, Pricing &amp;amp; Who Should Use It).</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2026/02/2026-02-03-whatconverts-the-complete-guide-to-lead-tracking-marketing-attribution-software-features-how-it-works-pricing-who-should-use-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2026/02/2026-02-03-whatconverts-the-complete-guide-to-lead-tracking-marketing-attribution-software-features-how-it-works-pricing-who-should-use-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Marketing teams today face one major challenge: &lt;strong&gt;proving which campaigns actually generate revenue&lt;/strong&gt;. WhatConverts solves this problem by giving businesses a single platform to track every lead—calls, forms, chats, and eCommerce events—and tie them back to the exact marketing source.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide breaks down how &lt;a href=&#34;https://partners.whatconverts.com/fyqohnw3xo8x&#34;&gt;WhatConverts&lt;/a&gt; works, its core features, who it’s built for, and the most up‑to‑date pricing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is &lt;a href=&#34;https://partners.whatconverts.com/fyqohnw3xo8x&#34;&gt;WhatConverts&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://partners.whatconverts.com/fyqohnw3xo8x&#34;&gt;WhatConverts&lt;/a&gt; is an all‑in‑one &lt;strong&gt;lead tracking, call tracking, and marketing attribution software&lt;/strong&gt; that helps businesses understand:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🚀 Boost Engagement with Manychat: The Smart Way to Automate Your Messaging</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/11/2025-11-17--boost-engagement-with-manychat-the-smart-way-to-automate-your-messaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/11/2025-11-17--boost-engagement-with-manychat-the-smart-way-to-automate-your-messaging/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://manychat.partnerlinks.io/2gpapavsqk9i&#34;&gt;Manychat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a leading chatbot platform designed to help businesses automate conversations across Instagram, Facebook Messenger, WhatsApp, and SMS. With its intuitive drag-and-drop interface, powerful integrations, and real-time analytics, Manychat empowers brands to scale customer interactions without sacrificing personalization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a solopreneur, e-commerce store, or agency, &lt;a href=&#34;https://manychat.partnerlinks.io/2gpapavsqk9i&#34;&gt;Manychat&lt;/a&gt; makes it easy to build automated flows that convert visitors into loyal customers — all without writing a single line of code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;✅ &lt;strong&gt;Get 30% off instantly&lt;/strong&gt; when you sign up through this link. No promo code needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🚀 What Is Lead Generation &amp;amp; The Best Free Tool to Supercharge Your Marketing.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/08/2025-08-28--what-is-lead-generation-the-best-free-tool-to-supercharge-your-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/08/2025-08-28--what-is-lead-generation-the-best-free-tool-to-supercharge-your-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s hyper-competitive digital landscape, one challenge haunts every business owner, marketer, and sales professional: &lt;strong&gt;how do you consistently generate quality leads&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re launching a new product, scaling your startup, or simply trying to grow your email list, lead generation is the lifeblood of your marketing efforts. But what exactly is lead generation—and how can you do it effectively without burning through your budget?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s break it down.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-what-is-lead-generation&#34;&gt;💡 What Is Lead Generation?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lead generation&lt;/strong&gt; is the process of attracting and converting strangers into potential customers who have shown interest in your product or service. These leads can come from various channels—social media, search engines, webinars, or even cold outreach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🚀 How to Generate Leads with Lead Magnets and Auto Funnels: The Modern Marketer’s Blueprint.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/08/2025-08-15--how-to-generate-leads-with-lead-magnets-and-auto-funnels-the-modern-marketers-blueprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/08/2025-08-15--how-to-generate-leads-with-lead-magnets-and-auto-funnels-the-modern-marketers-blueprint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s fast-paced digital landscape, capturing attention is only half the battle. The real victory lies in converting that attention into qualified leads—and ultimately, loyal customers. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a solopreneur, a startup, or a seasoned marketer, mastering the art of lead generation through &lt;strong&gt;lead magnets and auto funnels&lt;/strong&gt; is your ticket to scalable success.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-what-is-a-lead-magnet-and-why-it-works&#34;&gt;🎯 What Is a Lead Magnet and Why It Works&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;lead magnet&lt;/strong&gt; is a free resource offered in exchange for a visitor’s contact information—typically their email. Think of it as a value-packed handshake that initiates a relationship.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ManyChat: The Ultimate Messenger Bot Platform for Small Business Success.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/04/2025-04-15-manychat-the-ultimate-messenger-bot-platform-for-small-business-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/04/2025-04-15-manychat-the-ultimate-messenger-bot-platform-for-small-business-success/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the dynamic world of digital marketing, instant communication is the key to success. If you&amp;rsquo;re a small business owner striving to build stronger customer relationships and scale your brand, ManyChat is your answer. As the #1 bot platform for Facebook Messenger, ManyChat empowers businesses to connect, engage, and grow like never before.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Makes ManyChat #1?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;ManyChat isn’t just another chatbot platform—it&amp;rsquo;s a revolutionary tool trusted by 500,000 small businesses worldwide. Whether you want to automate responses, nurture leads, or boost sales, ManyChat delivers real-time interaction with millions of customers at scale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
