<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artificial-Intelligence on N Design Studio</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artificial-Intelligence on N Design Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building a Sharia‑Compliant Banking System with PostgreSQL: A Deep Dive into Modern Islamic Finance Engineering</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2026/01/2026-01-22-building-a-sharia-compliant-banking-system-with-postgresql-a-deep-dive-into-modern-islamic-finance-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2026/01/2026-01-22-building-a-sharia-compliant-banking-system-with-postgresql-a-deep-dive-into-modern-islamic-finance-engineering/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Islamic finance is one of the fastest‑growing sectors in global banking — yet high‑quality, open‑source systems that model real Sharia‑compliant workflows are rare. To bridge that gap, I built a &lt;strong&gt;Sharia‑Compliant Banking Management System (SCBMS)&lt;/strong&gt;: a fully structured PostgreSQL backend that models Islamic banking operations with accuracy, automation, and transparency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post walks through the key ideas behind the project, the architecture, and some of the SQL powering it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-why-build-a-shariacompliant-banking-system&#34;&gt;🌐 Why Build a Sharia‑Compliant Banking System?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Islamic finance operates on principles fundamentally different from conventional banking:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackbox AI – Features, Uses, and Pricing &#43; Free Prompt Demo and sticker design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/11/2025-11-23-blackbox-ai-features-uses-and-pricing-free-prompt-demo-and-sticker-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/11/2025-11-23-blackbox-ai-features-uses-and-pricing-free-prompt-demo-and-sticker-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-what-is-blackbox-ai&#34;&gt;📌 What is Blackbox AI?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blackboxai.partnerlinks.io/1uv6a6d3e89u&#34;&gt;Blackbox&lt;/a&gt; AI is an &lt;strong&gt;AI-powered coding assistant&lt;/strong&gt; designed to streamline software development. It leverages &lt;strong&gt;300+ AI models&lt;/strong&gt; and autonomous agents to help developers code smarter and faster. Unlike traditional code generators, Blackbox AI supports &lt;strong&gt;multi-modal capabilities&lt;/strong&gt; such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voice coding&lt;/strong&gt; – speak commands and generate code instantly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image-to-code conversion&lt;/strong&gt; – turn design mockups into functional code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-agent execution&lt;/strong&gt; – coordinate multiple AI agents for complex tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Web with ThorData: Proxy Power for Smart Scraping</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/11/2025-11-01-unlocking-the-web-with-thordata-proxy-power-for-smart-scraping/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/11/2025-11-01-unlocking-the-web-with-thordata-proxy-power-for-smart-scraping/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s data-driven world, accessing public web data efficiently and securely is a competitive advantage. &lt;em&gt;ThorData&lt;/em&gt;, founded in 2018 and headquartered in Hong Kong, has emerged as a leading provider of proxy services and scraping APIs tailored for businesses, developers, and analysts. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re tracking SEO rankings, monitoring prices, or training AI models, ThorData delivers scalable tools to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-thordata-products-and-services&#34;&gt;🛠️ &lt;a href=&#34;https://affiliate.thordata.com/vpn5dj496uy2&#34;&gt;ThorData&lt;/a&gt; Products and Services&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://affiliate.thordata.com/vpn5dj496uy2&#34;&gt;ThorData’&lt;/a&gt;s ecosystem is built around high-performance proxies and scraping APIs:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🚀 Most Popular AI Prompts That Boost Business Creativity in Marketing.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/08/2025-08-17--most-popular-ai-prompts-that-boost-business-creativity-in-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/08/2025-08-17--most-popular-ai-prompts-that-boost-business-creativity-in-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s fast-paced digital landscape, creativity is the lifeblood of successful marketing. But even the most brilliant minds hit creative blocks. That’s where AI steps in—not to replace marketers, but to supercharge their imagination. With the right prompts, AI tools can become powerful collaborators, helping businesses generate fresh ideas, streamline workflows, and connect more deeply with their audience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’ll explore the &lt;strong&gt;most popular AI prompts&lt;/strong&gt; that marketers are using to &lt;strong&gt;boost creativity and drive results&lt;/strong&gt;. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re crafting campaigns, writing content, or analyzing performance, these prompts will help you unlock new possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Journalist App for Windows: A Comprehensive Review.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2024/07/2024-07-26-exploring-the-journalist-app-for-windows-a-comprehensive-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2024/07/2024-07-26-exploring-the-journalist-app-for-windows-a-comprehensive-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving landscape of digital journalism, tools that streamline the writing, editing, and publishing process are invaluable. One such tool that has garnered attention is the Journalist app for Windows. This article delves into the features, benefits, and potential drawbacks of the Journalist app, providing a comprehensive review for those considering integrating it into their workflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction-to-the-journalist-app&#34;&gt;Introduction to the Journalist App&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Journalist app is a dedicated software designed to cater to the needs of modern journalists, writers, and content creators. Available on the Windows platform, this app aims to simplify the complexities of content creation, offering a suite of features that enhance productivity and ensure high-quality output.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
