<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on N Design Studio</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on N Design Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2026 N Design Studio. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building a Sharia‑Compliant Banking System with PostgreSQL: A Deep Dive into Modern Islamic Finance Engineering</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2026/01/2026-01-22-building-a-sharia-compliant-banking-system-with-postgresql-a-deep-dive-into-modern-islamic-finance-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2026/01/2026-01-22-building-a-sharia-compliant-banking-system-with-postgresql-a-deep-dive-into-modern-islamic-finance-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Islamic finance is one of the fastest‑growing sectors in global banking — yet high‑quality, open‑source systems that model real Sharia‑compliant workflows are rare. To bridge that gap, I built a Sharia‑Compliant Banking Management System (SCBMS): a fully structured PostgreSQL backend that models Islamic banking operations with accuracy, automation, and transparency.&#xA;This post walks through the key ideas behind the project, the architecture, and some of the SQL powering it.&#xA;🌐 Why Build a Sharia‑Compliant Banking System?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noon 11.11 Sale Extended! Grab These Top 10 Budget Phones with an Extra 15% Off</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-16-noon-11-11-sale-extended-grab-these-top-10-budget-phones-with-an-extra-15-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-16-noon-11-11-sale-extended-grab-these-top-10-budget-phones-with-an-extra-15-off/</guid>
      <description>Your Ultimate Guide to Smartphone Savings&#xA;The biggest sale of the year isn&amp;rsquo;t over yet! Noon.com has extended its spectacular 11.11 sale, giving you more time to snag incredible deals. If you’ve been waiting to upgrade your smartphone without breaking the bank, this is your golden opportunity.&#xA;We’ve scoured the sale to bring you the best budget-friendly phones that offer premium features without the premium price tag. From the trendy Nothing CMF Phone 1 to the reliable Vivo V50 Lite, there’s something for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🚀 Most Popular AI Prompts That Boost Business Creativity in Marketing.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/08/2025-08-17--most-popular-ai-prompts-that-boost-business-creativity-in-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/08/2025-08-17--most-popular-ai-prompts-that-boost-business-creativity-in-marketing/</guid>
      <description>In today’s fast-paced digital landscape, creativity is the lifeblood of successful marketing. But even the most brilliant minds hit creative blocks. That’s where AI steps in—not to replace marketers, but to supercharge their imagination. With the right prompts, AI tools can become powerful collaborators, helping businesses generate fresh ideas, streamline workflows, and connect more deeply with their audience.&#xA;In this post, we’ll explore the most popular AI prompts that marketers are using to boost creativity and drive results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to the Best Laptops in the Middle East (2025).</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/06/2025-06-04-the-ultimate-guide-to-the-best-laptops-in-the-middle-east-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/06/2025-06-04-the-ultimate-guide-to-the-best-laptops-in-the-middle-east-2025/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to our blog, we took a time off to finish our studies. In this blog post we have prepared for you a handpicked guide towards owning your dream laptop from Noon Middle East.&#xA;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a student, a professional, or a hardcore gamer, choosing the right laptop can be overwhelming. The Middle East market offers a wide range of options, from budget-friendly models to high-end gaming beasts. To help you decide, we’ve categorized the best laptops available right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of NDesignStudio&#39;s Drawings of the Month of August.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/08/2024-08-30-review-of-ndesignstudios-drawings-of-the-month-of-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/08/2024-08-30-review-of-ndesignstudios-drawings-of-the-month-of-august/</guid>
      <description>In this article I will post the drawings I made in the month of august, created by the journalist app. Thank you for your support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Journalist App for Windows: A Comprehensive Review.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/07/2024-07-26-exploring-the-journalist-app-for-windows-a-comprehensive-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/07/2024-07-26-exploring-the-journalist-app-for-windows-a-comprehensive-review/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving landscape of digital journalism, tools that streamline the writing, editing, and publishing process are invaluable. One such tool that has garnered attention is the Journalist app for Windows. This article delves into the features, benefits, and potential drawbacks of the Journalist app, providing a comprehensive review for those considering integrating it into their workflow.&#xA;Introduction to the Journalist App The Journalist app is a dedicated software designed to cater to the needs of modern journalists, writers, and content creators.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
