<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>website on N Design Studio</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/categories/website/</link><description>Recent content in website on N Design Studio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2026 N Design Studio. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/categories/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Backup Multiple PCs, Macs, and Mobile Devices into One Account with IDrive</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-25-backup-multiple-pcs-macs-and-mobile-devices-into-one-account-with-idrive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-25-backup-multiple-pcs-macs-and-mobile-devices-into-one-account-with-idrive/</guid><description>When it comes to protecting your digital life, IDrive stands out as one of the most versatile cloud backup solutions. Whether you’re a freelancer juggling multiple devices, a family safeguarding memories, or a small business managing critical files, IDrive makes it simple to back up all your PCs, Macs, and mobile devices into one secure account.
Why Choose IDrive? Cross-platform support: Backup Windows, macOS, iOS, and Android seamlessly.
One account, unlimited devices: No need to juggle multiple subscriptions.</description></item><item><title>Blackbox AI – Features, Uses, and Pricing + Free Prompt Demo and sticker design</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-23-blackbox-ai-features-uses-and-pricing-free-prompt-demo-and-sticker-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-23-blackbox-ai-features-uses-and-pricing-free-prompt-demo-and-sticker-design/</guid><description>📌 What is Blackbox AI? Blackbox AI is an AI-powered coding assistant designed to streamline software development. It leverages 300+ AI models and autonomous agents to help developers code smarter and faster. Unlike traditional code generators, Blackbox AI supports multi-modal capabilities such as:
Voice coding – speak commands and generate code instantly.
Image-to-code conversion – turn design mockups into functional code.
Multi-agent execution – coordinate multiple AI agents for complex tasks.</description></item><item><title>🌐 From Dreamer to Digital Creator: How SitesGPT Empowers Non-Techies to Build Stunning Websites.</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-09--from-dreamer-to-digital-creator-how-sitesgpt-empowers-non-techies-to-build-stunning-websites/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-09--from-dreamer-to-digital-creator-how-sitesgpt-empowers-non-techies-to-build-stunning-websites/</guid><description>✨ Meet Layla: The Dreamer Who Thought She Couldn’t Build a Website Layla always had a vision. A small online shop selling handmade jewelry inspired by Turkish poetry and Mediterranean colors. But every time she tried to build a website, she hit a wall—HTML, CSS, hosting plans, plugins&amp;hellip; it was overwhelming.
She wasn’t a developer. She wasn’t a designer. She was a creator with a dream.
Then she discovered SitesGPT—an AI-powered website builder that changed everything.</description></item></channel></rss>