<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web-Hosting on N Design Studio</title>
    <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/categories/web-hosting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web-Hosting on N Design Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2026 N Design Studio. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/categories/web-hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Plesk Black Friday 2025: Save 50% on Hosting Licenses</title>
      <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-28-plesk-black-friday-2025-save-50-on-hosting-licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-28-plesk-black-friday-2025-save-50-on-hosting-licenses/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve been waiting to streamline your web hosting management, Plesk’s Black Friday promotion is officially live! From November 24 to December 1, 2025, new users and active trial accounts can enjoy 50% off the first period on all monthly and yearly licenses. Simply apply the promo code blackfriday2025 at checkout to claim your discount.&#xA;🎯 Promotion Details Offer: 50% off first period (monthly &amp;amp; yearly licenses)&#xA;Promo code: blackfriday2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plesk: The Server Management Platform Built With You in Mind</title>
      <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-09-plesk-the-server-management-platform-built-with-you-in-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-09-plesk-the-server-management-platform-built-with-you-in-mind/</guid>
      <description>Managing servers shouldn’t feel like rocket science. That’s why Plesk has become one of the most trusted server management platforms worldwide. With its fully integrated dynamic monitoring dashboards, Plesk empowers web professionals, hosting providers, and businesses to streamline operations, boost performance, and secure their digital assets—all from one intuitive interface.&#xA;🌟 Why Choose Plesk? Centralized Control: Plesk offers a clean, graphical interface to manage websites, domains, databases, and email accounts without needing deep command-line expertise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🌐 From Dreamer to Digital Creator: How SitesGPT Empowers Non-Techies to Build Stunning Websites.</title>
      <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-09--from-dreamer-to-digital-creator-how-sitesgpt-empowers-non-techies-to-build-stunning-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-09--from-dreamer-to-digital-creator-how-sitesgpt-empowers-non-techies-to-build-stunning-websites/</guid>
      <description>✨ Meet Layla: The Dreamer Who Thought She Couldn’t Build a Website Layla always had a vision. A small online shop selling handmade jewelry inspired by Turkish poetry and Mediterranean colors. But every time she tried to build a website, she hit a wall—HTML, CSS, hosting plans, plugins&amp;hellip; it was overwhelming.&#xA;She wasn’t a developer. She wasn’t a designer. She was a creator with a dream.&#xA;Then she discovered SitesGPT—an AI-powered website builder that changed everything.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
