<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crafts on N Design Studio</title>
    <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/tags/crafts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crafts on N Design Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2026 N Design Studio. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/tags/crafts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Timeless Art of Crochet with Wedad Kn.: A Journey Through History, Techniques, and Creativity.</title>
      <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/03/2025-03-15-discover-the-timeless-art-of-crochet-with-wedad-kn-a-journey-through-history-techniques-and-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/03/2025-03-15-discover-the-timeless-art-of-crochet-with-wedad-kn-a-journey-through-history-techniques-and-creativity/</guid>
      <description>Crochet is more than just a craft—it’s a timeless art form that weaves together history, culture, and creativity. If you’ve ever marveled at the intricate patterns of a crocheted blanket or the delicate beauty of a handmade doily, you’ve witnessed the magic of this centuries-old technique. Today, we’re diving into the world of crochet, exploring its rich history, diverse techniques, and the inspiring work of Wedad Kn., a talented crochet artist whose Instagram account (@Wedadsart) is a must-follow for anyone who loves handmade artistry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Handmade Friendship Bracelets Are Taking Over Istanbul 2025!</title>
      <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/03/2025-03-06-these-handmade-friendship-bracelets-are-taking-over-istanbul-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/03/2025-03-06-these-handmade-friendship-bracelets-are-taking-over-istanbul-2025/</guid>
      <description>In a world that often feels vast and disconnected, NDesignstudio brings people closer together—one bracelet at a time. Founded by the creative visionary Nemah Alsayed, NDesignstudio specializes in handcrafted friendship bracelets that are more than just accessories; they are wearable stories, symbols of unity, and celebrations of global diversity.&#xA;Each bracelet is meticulously crafted with beads and threads, carefully chosen to represent the unique colors and cultural DNA of countries around the world.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
