<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>technology on N Design Studio</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/tags/technology/</link><description>Recent content in technology on N Design Studio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2026 N Design Studio. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building a Sharia‑Compliant Banking System with PostgreSQL: A Deep Dive into Modern Islamic Finance Engineering</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2026/01/2026-01-22-building-a-sharia-compliant-banking-system-with-postgresql-a-deep-dive-into-modern-islamic-finance-engineering/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2026/01/2026-01-22-building-a-sharia-compliant-banking-system-with-postgresql-a-deep-dive-into-modern-islamic-finance-engineering/</guid><description>Islamic finance is one of the fastest‑growing sectors in global banking — yet high‑quality, open‑source systems that model real Sharia‑compliant workflows are rare. To bridge that gap, I built a Sharia‑Compliant Banking Management System (SCBMS): a fully structured PostgreSQL backend that models Islamic banking operations with accuracy, automation, and transparency.
This post walks through the key ideas behind the project, the architecture, and some of the SQL powering it.
🌐 Why Build a Sharia‑Compliant Banking System?</description></item><item><title>CloudTalk Review: A Smart, Scalable Call Center Solution for Modern Teams</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2026/01/2026-01-07-cloudtalk-review-a-smart-scalable-call-center-solution-for-modern-teams/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2026/01/2026-01-07-cloudtalk-review-a-smart-scalable-call-center-solution-for-modern-teams/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re searching for a cloud-based phone system that blends reliability, advanced features, and affordability, CloudTalk is one of the standout names in the market. In this light review, we’ll explore who CloudTalk is, what services they offer, why their pricing is competitive, and who can benefit most from using their platform. You’ll also find a placeholder for your affiliate link so you can easily integrate it into your content strategy.</description></item><item><title>Plesk Black Friday 2025: Save 50% on Hosting Licenses</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-28-plesk-black-friday-2025-save-50-on-hosting-licenses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-28-plesk-black-friday-2025-save-50-on-hosting-licenses/</guid><description>If you’ve been waiting to streamline your web hosting management, Plesk’s Black Friday promotion is officially live! From November 24 to December 1, 2025, new users and active trial accounts can enjoy 50% off the first period on all monthly and yearly licenses. Simply apply the promo code blackfriday2025 at checkout to claim your discount.
🎯 Promotion Details Offer: 50% off first period (monthly &amp;amp; yearly licenses)
Promo code: blackfriday2025</description></item><item><title>Blackbox AI – Features, Uses, and Pricing + Free Prompt Demo and sticker design</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-23-blackbox-ai-features-uses-and-pricing-free-prompt-demo-and-sticker-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-23-blackbox-ai-features-uses-and-pricing-free-prompt-demo-and-sticker-design/</guid><description>📌 What is Blackbox AI? Blackbox AI is an AI-powered coding assistant designed to streamline software development. It leverages 300+ AI models and autonomous agents to help developers code smarter and faster. Unlike traditional code generators, Blackbox AI supports multi-modal capabilities such as:
Voice coding – speak commands and generate code instantly.
Image-to-code conversion – turn design mockups into functional code.
Multi-agent execution – coordinate multiple AI agents for complex tasks.</description></item><item><title>Noon 11.11 Sale Extended! Grab These Top 10 Budget Phones with an Extra 15% Off</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-16-noon-11-11-sale-extended-grab-these-top-10-budget-phones-with-an-extra-15-off/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-16-noon-11-11-sale-extended-grab-these-top-10-budget-phones-with-an-extra-15-off/</guid><description>Your Ultimate Guide to Smartphone Savings
The biggest sale of the year isn&amp;rsquo;t over yet! Noon.com has extended its spectacular 11.11 sale, giving you more time to snag incredible deals. If you’ve been waiting to upgrade your smartphone without breaking the bank, this is your golden opportunity.
We’ve scoured the sale to bring you the best budget-friendly phones that offer premium features without the premium price tag. From the trendy Nothing CMF Phone 1 to the reliable Vivo V50 Lite, there’s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Plesk: The Server Management Platform Built With You in Mind</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-09-plesk-the-server-management-platform-built-with-you-in-mind/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-09-plesk-the-server-management-platform-built-with-you-in-mind/</guid><description>Managing servers shouldn’t feel like rocket science. That’s why Plesk has become one of the most trusted server management platforms worldwide. With its fully integrated dynamic monitoring dashboards, Plesk empowers web professionals, hosting providers, and businesses to streamline operations, boost performance, and secure their digital assets—all from one intuitive interface.
🌟 Why Choose Plesk? Centralized Control: Plesk offers a clean, graphical interface to manage websites, domains, databases, and email accounts without needing deep command-line expertise.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking the Web with ThorData: Proxy Power for Smart Scraping</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-01-unlocking-the-web-with-thordata-proxy-power-for-smart-scraping/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-01-unlocking-the-web-with-thordata-proxy-power-for-smart-scraping/</guid><description>In today’s data-driven world, accessing public web data efficiently and securely is a competitive advantage. ThorData, founded in 2018 and headquartered in Hong Kong, has emerged as a leading provider of proxy services and scraping APIs tailored for businesses, developers, and analysts. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re tracking SEO rankings, monitoring prices, or training AI models, ThorData delivers scalable tools to meet your needs.
🛠️ ThorData Products and Services ThorData’s ecosystem is built around high-performance proxies and scraping APIs:</description></item><item><title>🧠 WebCatalog Review 2025: The Ultimate App &amp;amp; Account Manager for Digital Pros.</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-14--webcatalog-review-2025-the-ultimate-app-account-manager-for-digital-pros/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-14--webcatalog-review-2025-the-ultimate-app-account-manager-for-digital-pros/</guid><description>In today’s hyper-connected world, juggling multiple apps, accounts, and workflows can feel like digital chaos. Enter WebCatalog—a sleek, privacy-first platform designed to bring order to your online universe. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a freelancer, marketer, developer, or just someone tired of browser tab overload, WebCatalog might be the productivity upgrade you didn’t know you needed.
🚀 What Is WebCatalog? WebCatalog transforms any website into a standalone desktop app, allowing users to manage multiple accounts, receive unified notifications, and eliminate distractions.</description></item><item><title>🚀 Trainual Review 2025: The Ultimate SOP &amp;amp; Onboarding Tool for Growing Teams.</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-13--trainual-review-2025-the-ultimate-sop-onboarding-tool-for-growing-teams/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-13--trainual-review-2025-the-ultimate-sop-onboarding-tool-for-growing-teams/</guid><description>In today’s fast-paced digital workplace, documenting processes and training new hires efficiently is no longer a luxury—it’s a necessity. That’s where Trainual comes in. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re scaling a startup, managing remote teams, or streamlining operations in a multilingual environment, Trainual offers a centralized solution to keep your business aligned, productive, and compliant.
🧠 What Is Trainual? Trainual is a cloud-based training and process documentation platform designed to help businesses create, manage, and deliver Standard Operating Procedures (SOPs), onboarding materials, and internal knowledge—all in one place.</description></item><item><title>🚀 Most Popular AI Prompts That Boost Business Creativity in Marketing.</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/08/2025-08-17--most-popular-ai-prompts-that-boost-business-creativity-in-marketing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/08/2025-08-17--most-popular-ai-prompts-that-boost-business-creativity-in-marketing/</guid><description>In today’s fast-paced digital landscape, creativity is the lifeblood of successful marketing. But even the most brilliant minds hit creative blocks. That’s where AI steps in—not to replace marketers, but to supercharge their imagination. With the right prompts, AI tools can become powerful collaborators, helping businesses generate fresh ideas, streamline workflows, and connect more deeply with their audience.
In this post, we’ll explore the most popular AI prompts that marketers are using to boost creativity and drive results.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Guide to the Best Laptops in the Middle East (2025).</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/06/2025-06-04-the-ultimate-guide-to-the-best-laptops-in-the-middle-east-2025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/06/2025-06-04-the-ultimate-guide-to-the-best-laptops-in-the-middle-east-2025/</guid><description>Welcome back to our blog, we took a time off to finish our studies. In this blog post we have prepared for you a handpicked guide towards owning your dream laptop from Noon Middle East.
Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a student, a professional, or a hardcore gamer, choosing the right laptop can be overwhelming. The Middle East market offers a wide range of options, from budget-friendly models to high-end gaming beasts. To help you decide, we’ve categorized the best laptops available right now.</description></item><item><title>ManyChat: The Ultimate Messenger Bot Platform for Small Business Success.</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/04/2025-04-15-manychat-the-ultimate-messenger-bot-platform-for-small-business-success/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/04/2025-04-15-manychat-the-ultimate-messenger-bot-platform-for-small-business-success/</guid><description>In the dynamic world of digital marketing, instant communication is the key to success. If you&amp;rsquo;re a small business owner striving to build stronger customer relationships and scale your brand, ManyChat is your answer. As the #1 bot platform for Facebook Messenger, ManyChat empowers businesses to connect, engage, and grow like never before.
What Makes ManyChat #1?
ManyChat isn’t just another chatbot platform—it&amp;rsquo;s a revolutionary tool trusted by 500,000 small businesses worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Review of NDesignStudio's Drawings of the Month of August.</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2024/08/2024-08-30-review-of-ndesignstudios-drawings-of-the-month-of-august/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2024/08/2024-08-30-review-of-ndesignstudios-drawings-of-the-month-of-august/</guid><description>In this article I will post the drawings I made in the month of august, created by the journalist app. Thank you for your support.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the Journalist App for Windows: A Comprehensive Review.</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2024/07/2024-07-26-exploring-the-journalist-app-for-windows-a-comprehensive-review/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2024/07/2024-07-26-exploring-the-journalist-app-for-windows-a-comprehensive-review/</guid><description>In the ever-evolving landscape of digital journalism, tools that streamline the writing, editing, and publishing process are invaluable. One such tool that has garnered attention is the Journalist app for Windows. This article delves into the features, benefits, and potential drawbacks of the Journalist app, providing a comprehensive review for those considering integrating it into their workflow.
Introduction to the Journalist App The Journalist app is a dedicated software designed to cater to the needs of modern journalists, writers, and content creators.</description></item></channel></rss>