<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on N Design Studio</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/categories/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on N Design Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2026 N Design Studio. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/categories/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🌐 From Dreamer to Digital Creator: How SitesGPT Empowers Non-Techies to Build Stunning Websites.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-09--from-dreamer-to-digital-creator-how-sitesgpt-empowers-non-techies-to-build-stunning-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-09--from-dreamer-to-digital-creator-how-sitesgpt-empowers-non-techies-to-build-stunning-websites/</guid>
      <description>✨ Meet Layla: The Dreamer Who Thought She Couldn’t Build a Website Layla always had a vision. A small online shop selling handmade jewelry inspired by Turkish poetry and Mediterranean colors. But every time she tried to build a website, she hit a wall—HTML, CSS, hosting plans, plugins&amp;hellip; it was overwhelming.&#xA;She wasn’t a developer. She wasn’t a designer. She was a creator with a dream.&#xA;Then she discovered SitesGPT—an AI-powered website builder that changed everything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NFT Art- April 2025.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/_drafts/2025/04/2025-04-13-new-nft-art-april-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/_drafts/2025/04/2025-04-13-new-nft-art-april-2025/</guid>
      <description>This art symbolizes the rich wisdoms of Mavlana Jalal El-din Al-Rumi in a Mystic Sufi Poem as the following:&#xA;A New Rule&#xA;It is the rule with drunkards to fall upon each other,&#xA;to quarrel, become violent, and make a scene.&#xA;The lover is even worse than a drunkard.&#xA;I will tell you what love is: to enter a mine of gold.&#xA;And what is that gold?&#xA;The lover is a king above all kings,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of NDesignStudio&#39;s Drawings of the Month of August.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/08/2024-08-30-review-of-ndesignstudios-drawings-of-the-month-of-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/08/2024-08-30-review-of-ndesignstudios-drawings-of-the-month-of-august/</guid>
      <description>In this article I will post the drawings I made in the month of august, created by the journalist app. Thank you for your support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Review; July Drawings.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/_drafts/2024/07/2024-07-31-monthly-review-july-drawings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/_drafts/2024/07/2024-07-31-monthly-review-july-drawings/</guid>
      <description>In this monthly review we will show the drawings of our studio for the month of July. The drawings are created by the journalist app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Journalist App for Windows: A Comprehensive Review.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/07/2024-07-26-exploring-the-journalist-app-for-windows-a-comprehensive-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/07/2024-07-26-exploring-the-journalist-app-for-windows-a-comprehensive-review/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving landscape of digital journalism, tools that streamline the writing, editing, and publishing process are invaluable. One such tool that has garnered attention is the Journalist app for Windows. This article delves into the features, benefits, and potential drawbacks of the Journalist app, providing a comprehensive review for those considering integrating it into their workflow.&#xA;Introduction to the Journalist App The Journalist app is a dedicated software designed to cater to the needs of modern journalists, writers, and content creators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Design Brief for Design Project Made for Production;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/03/2024-03-10-how-to-create-design-brief-for-design-project-made-for-production/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/posts/2024/03/2024-03-10-how-to-create-design-brief-for-design-project-made-for-production/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s post I will share with you how to create a design brief to participate in international competition held by an Italian university called Poli.Design; Save this post for future competition dates, specially if you are a design or industrial design student;&#xA;The challenge of this competition was to design different types of chairs, interpreting values and identity of Porada, and the guidelines that will inspire the partecipants will be innovation, originality and search of new design solutions for woodworking.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
