<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My-Paintings on N Design Studio</title>
    <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/categories/my-paintings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My-Paintings on N Design Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2026 N Design Studio. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/categories/my-paintings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🌸 Metal Art Sheet Flower Abstract Landscape Painting – A Modern Statement Piece</title>
      <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/12/2025-12-20--metal-art-sheet-flower-abstract-landscape-painting-a-modern-statement-piece/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/12/2025-12-20--metal-art-sheet-flower-abstract-landscape-painting-a-modern-statement-piece/</guid>
      <description>A Fusion of Metal and Canvas Art has always been about pushing boundaries, and this Metal Art Sheet Flower Abstract Landscape Painting is a perfect example. Crafted with acrylic on canvas (30×40 cm), it blends traditional painting techniques with the bold texture of metal sheets. The result? A one‑of‑a‑kind artwork that radiates elegance and modernity.&#xA;The Design: Abstract Meets Nature This piece features an abstract background adorned with three delicate flowers, symbolizing growth, beauty, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Months artwork by nemah;</title>
      <link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/04/2025-04-07-latest-months-artwork-by-nemah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/04/2025-04-07-latest-months-artwork-by-nemah/</guid>
      <description>Hello to all my new followers of my blog, in this post I will share with you the latest paintings I have been working on for the last couple of months; their theme and story behind them. Enjoy!&#xA;The first one is a circular canvas that represents a clock; I have added mechanical clock pieces on the canvas to make it a wall clock.&#xA;The second and third ones represents the historical town of Jableh in Syria with pronounced elements of the city such as Roman theater and Sufi Mosque arches with white Greek dome architecture style.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
