<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Art on N Design Studio</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/tags/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Art on N Design Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/tags/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🔮 Breathing Digital Life into Rumi: My NFT Tribute to “Any Lifetime”.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/08/2025-08-29--breathing-digital-life-into-rumi-my-nft-tribute-to-any-lifetime/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/08/2025-08-29--breathing-digital-life-into-rumi-my-nft-tribute-to-any-lifetime/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a world increasingly shaped by pixels and blockchain, I wanted to create something that transcends the digital — something that speaks to the soul. That’s how my latest NFT artwork was born: a visual meditation on Mewlana Jalaluddin Rumi’s poem &lt;em&gt;“Any Lifetime.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;-the-poem-that-sparked-a-vision&#34;&gt;🧠 The Poem That Sparked a Vision&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Any lifetime that is spent without seeing the master&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Is either death in disguise or a deep sleep.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;The water that pollutes you is poison;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;The poison that purifies you is water.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NFT Art- April 2025.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/_drafts/2025/04/2025-04-13-new-nft-art-april-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/_drafts/2025/04/2025-04-13-new-nft-art-april-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This art symbolizes the rich wisdoms of Mavlana Jalal El-din Al-Rumi in a Mystic Sufi Poem as the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A New Rule&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It is the rule with drunkards to fall upon each other,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;to quarrel, become violent, and make a scene.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The lover is even worse than a drunkard.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I will tell you what love is: to enter a mine of gold.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And what is that gold?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The lover is a king above all kings,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;unafraid of death, not at all interested in a golden crown.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The dervish has a pearl concealed under his patched cloak.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Why should he go begging door to door?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Last night that moon came along,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;drunk, dropping clothes in the street.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Get up,&amp;rdquo; I told my heart, &amp;ldquo;Give the soul a glass of wine.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The moment has come to join the nightingale in the garden,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;to taste sugar with the soul-parrot.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I have fallen, with my heart shattered -&#xA;where else but on your path? And I&lt;br&gt;&#xA;broke your bowl, drunk, my idol, so drunk,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;don&amp;rsquo;t let me be harmed, take my hand.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;A new rule a new law has been born:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;break all the glasses and fall toward the glassblower.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Mewlana Jalaluddin Rumi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🌟 Discover Unique Treasures at My Dolap Mini Store! 🌟</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/03/2025-03-27--discover-unique-treasures-at-my-dolap-mini-store-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/03/2025-03-27--discover-unique-treasures-at-my-dolap-mini-store-/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you on the hunt for one-of-a-kind art, creative coloring books, stylish clothing, or high-quality cosmetics? Look no further! My &lt;strong&gt;Dolap mini store&lt;/strong&gt; is your go-to destination for unique and handcrafted items that add a special touch to your life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;-handmade-art-paintings&#34;&gt;🎨 &lt;strong&gt;Handmade Art Paintings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bring beauty into your home with my &lt;strong&gt;original art pieces&lt;/strong&gt;! Each painting is crafted with passion, perfect for adding a personal and artistic vibe to any space. Whether you love abstract, modern, or classic styles, there’s something here for every art lover.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Timeless Art of Crochet with Wedad Kn.: A Journey Through History, Techniques, and Creativity.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/03/2025-03-15-discover-the-timeless-art-of-crochet-with-wedad-kn-a-journey-through-history-techniques-and-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/03/2025-03-15-discover-the-timeless-art-of-crochet-with-wedad-kn-a-journey-through-history-techniques-and-creativity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Crochet is more than just a craft—it’s a timeless art form that weaves together history, culture, and creativity. If you’ve ever marveled at the intricate patterns of a crocheted blanket or the delicate beauty of a handmade doily, you’ve witnessed the magic of this centuries-old technique. Today, we’re diving into the world of crochet, exploring its rich history, diverse techniques, and the inspiring work of &lt;strong&gt;Wedad Kn&lt;/strong&gt;., a talented crochet artist whose Instagram account (@Wedadsart) is a must-follow for anyone who loves handmade artistry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Handmade Friendship Bracelets Are Taking Over Istanbul 2025!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/03/2025-03-06-these-handmade-friendship-bracelets-are-taking-over-istanbul-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/NDesignstudyosu/en/en/post/2025/03/2025-03-06-these-handmade-friendship-bracelets-are-taking-over-istanbul-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a world that often feels vast and disconnected, NDesignstudio brings people closer together—one bracelet at a time. Founded by the creative visionary Nemah Alsayed, NDesignstudio specializes in handcrafted friendship bracelets that are more than just accessories; they are wearable stories, symbols of unity, and celebrations of global diversity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each bracelet is meticulously crafted with beads and threads, carefully chosen to represent the unique colors and cultural DNA of countries around the world. Whether it’s the vibrant hues of Mexico, the serene tones of Scandinavia, or the bold patterns of Africa, every piece tells a story. But that’s not all—Nemah adds a personal touch by including inspirational stickers and quotes with every purchase, making these bracelets not just a gift, but a meaningful experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
