<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>online-shopping on N Design Studio</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/categories/online-shopping/</link><description>Recent content in online-shopping on N Design Studio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2026 N Design Studio. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/categories/online-shopping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Noon 11.11 Sale Extended! Grab These Top 10 Budget Phones with an Extra 15% Off</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-16-noon-11-11-sale-extended-grab-these-top-10-budget-phones-with-an-extra-15-off/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/11/2025-11-16-noon-11-11-sale-extended-grab-these-top-10-budget-phones-with-an-extra-15-off/</guid><description>Your Ultimate Guide to Smartphone Savings
The biggest sale of the year isn&amp;rsquo;t over yet! Noon.com has extended its spectacular 11.11 sale, giving you more time to snag incredible deals. If you’ve been waiting to upgrade your smartphone without breaking the bank, this is your golden opportunity.
We’ve scoured the sale to bring you the best budget-friendly phones that offer premium features without the premium price tag. From the trendy Nothing CMF Phone 1 to the reliable Vivo V50 Lite, there’s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Unlock Digital Wealth: Why Flippa Is the Go-To Marketplace for Buying and Selling Online Businesses.</title><link>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-20-unlock-digital-wealth-why-flippa-is-the-go-to-marketplace-for-buying-and-selling-online-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nemahalsayed.github.io/NDesignstudyosu/en/posts/2025/09/2025-09-20-unlock-digital-wealth-why-flippa-is-the-go-to-marketplace-for-buying-and-selling-online-businesses/</guid><description>In today’s digital economy, owning an online business isn’t just a dream—it’s a strategic investment. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned entrepreneur, a side hustler, or a first-time buyer, Flippa offers a powerful platform to buy, sell, and grow digital assets. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to enter the world of online business ownership or cash out on a digital venture, Flippa is your gateway to opportunity.
What Is Flippa? Flippa is the world’s leading marketplace for buying and selling online businesses.</description></item></channel></rss>